vebsi.com 2014-11-22

# Vebsi - Terms Of Service

### Privacy Policy

Welcome to privacy policy governed by Vebsi.com. This page will explain all the rules and regulations along with your rights on Vebsi.com and its usage. This page has been made precise and explicit for all the users so please read it carefully as you will be bound to practice the content while using this website.

**A.** Types of Information We Collect We collect certain personal information about you, only when the information is provided by the user or that is obtained by us with your authorization. We collect just nominal information like IP address of the user..

**B.** Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell trade or transfer your information that is with us. This also includes all the third parties that assist us in operating our websites, our business or that are linked to us by any means except if parties agree to keep the information confidential. If we release any information it completely complies with the law, enforces our website policies and protects the rights of everyone.

**C.** Confidentiality and Security of Nonpublic Personal Information We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about our users to admins of our website and other parties who must use that information to provide services to you. Their right to further disclose and use the information is limited by the policies of our firm, applicable law, our Code of Professional Conduct and nondisclosure agreements where appropriate.  We also maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable laws and regulations to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, alteration or damage. 

**Third Party Links:** Occasionally, we may include third party products or services at our website. These parties have separate privacy policies. We therefore have no liability and responsibility of the links of all such websites. However, we seek to product the integrity of our website and at the same time welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**Disclaimer:** Vebsi.com has a lot of information that have been added by us or our visitors. We carefully draft all the information and try to correct any mistake, if found any, at the earliest. Use of any information on this website is strictly prohibited and against government law. 

**Your Consent:** By using our website, you consent to our privacy policy and all its associated rules. Changes to Our Privacy Policy: Whenever we change any policy, we will post the change on our page. This policy was last modified at 11/8/2013
